Morning.
Ooh, Cap'n Crunch.
That's the only man
I put in my mouth.
It puts my relationship
with Orville Redenbacher
in a whole different light.
I'm partial to the U.P.S. guy.
We're making food jokes here.
The U.P.S. guy's not food.
He is if you cover him
with whipped cream.
What can I say?
There's just something
about a man in brown shorts.
Okay, I'm in big trouble.
Speaking of a man
with brown shorts.
What's wrong?
Well, I just got a call
from Lyndsey's boyfriend Larry.
And he wants to see me.
Well, he wants
to see Jeff Strongman.
Who's Jeff Strongman?
Oh, Jeff Strongman
is Alan's alter ego he uses
to meet Larry and fight crime.
Wait, so, you use a fake name
to sneak around with other men?
Where do you guys meet?
A Lady Gaga concert?
It was a spin class
if you must know.
Now, what am I gonna do?
I told you something
like this was gonna happen.
(mocking): "I told you something like this
was gonna happen."
Look, I am serious-- he wouldn't
tell me why he wanted to see me
and he sounded pretty upset.
Well, what kind of world
are we living in
where a guy is upset
with another guy
for banging his girlfriend?
See, that's why
I love being gay.
A guy finds out
I'm doing his girlfriend,
I don't get an angry phone call.
I get a dozen roses
and a copy of the video.
Too bad I can't convince
Larry I'm gay.
Come on, Zippy, you're making it
too easy for us.
Oh, hey!
There he is.
My main man with a winter tan.
Jeff.
Uh, I got you a coffee.
Can I get you anything else?
Uh, one-one of these muffins?
They're bran.
Keeps your trains
running on time.
Poop-poop!
I'm not hungry.
All right then, I'll just
sit across from you.
Right here...
in front
of all these witnesses.
You know my girlfriend Lyndsey?
Is it Lyndsey?
I thought it was Linda.
Glad you cleared that up
before I saw her again...
which I haven't,
and why would I?
She's been cheating on me.
(hacking)
Mmm, sorry.
Just a little...
(clears throat)
Why do you think
she's cheating on you?
I hired a private investigator
to follow her.
(hacking)
Uh, do you mind?
She's been meeting him
at a house in Malibu.
Sorry, sorry,
I'm just a little shocked.
Imagine how I feel.
Well, I-I can't,
uh, uh, but I do know
that in situations like this,
it's the woman who's to blame.
She's not the only one.
Please, I have a son!
This is the guy.
Wait, this is the guy?
Yeah.
This is guy you think
banging your girlfriend?
I know he is.
And only him?
Nobody else?
Isn't this bad enough?
Well, sure.
But, you know, there could
also be another explanation.
I mean, maybe she's just lost
and she's asking
this guy for directions.
Right, "Excuse me, sir,
can you help me find my G-spot?"
It's not just this photo.
It's the late night errands.
Hiding her phone.
Plus, we haven't had sex
in forever!
Wow, that's rough.
I guess this guy, whoever he is,
satisfies her every need.
I want to kill him.
I hate being
lied to like this.
I get it, you know.
Sometimes you think you know
a person, but you don't.
Panini for Strongman.
Jeff, that's you.
What?
Oh, oh, yeah, that's me.
Jeff Strongman.
Someone who's not banging
anyone's girlfriend.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x08 ♪
Mr. Walden, He Die. I Clean Room.
Original Air Date on November 21, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, no, there's a stranger
in my house.
And it's possibly
a gay porn star from the '70s.
It's me, Alan.
I-I believe you're
supposed to say,
(Italian accent):
"It's-a me, a-Mario!"
So, I take it things
didn't go great with Larry?
Well, he does know
that Lyndsey's cheating on him,
but the good news is he doesn't
know that it's with me.
So, why do you look
like one of the Village People
in street clothes?
Ah, well, uh, he hired
a, uh, a private detective,
uh, to watch
the house because, uh,
and here's where it gets
really funny,
um, uh,
he thinks that Lyndsey is
cheating on him with...
No.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's crazy, right?
Why didn't you
tell him the truth?
Fear, cowardice.
Lack of a dental plan.
Uh, besides, he-he
just lost Lyndsey,
I didn't want him to
lose his best friend.
Okay, well, you're gonna lose
your best friend
if you don't fix this!
Oh, I'm your best friend?
Alan, I am serious.
I do not want a private
detective watching this house.
And I...
and I definitely don't want
an angry boyfriend after me.
Well, you should've
thought of that
before you slept with Lyndsey.
I've got some work to do.
And I'm gonna go out
and run some errands.
And when I get back,
this better be cleaned up.
Oh, oh, don't worry, I'm on it.
Oh, oh, but just in case.
Oh, God!
Is there any look
you can't pull off?
(Italian accent):
I'm-a gonna kill you.
Hey!
Hi-ya!
Oh!
What the hell?
Alan, what are you doing?
At the moment,
looking for my left ball.
Larry just dropped me off.
He could've seen you.
That's why I'm here.
Larry thinks you're
having an affair with Walden.
What? Why would he think that?
Well, because he he hired a P.I.
who t a picture of the two
of you together.
And by the way, it looked
like it was a cold day.
You're an idiot.
I know.
So, what-what are we gonna do?
Okay, look, I've done this
plenty of times before.
The first thing you do
is deny everything.
Right, denial. Wait.
You've done this
plenty of times before?
Did you ever cheat on me?
Never.
Okay, good.
(phone chirps)
Oh!
Oh, it's Larry.
What does he want?
Uh, well, let's see.
Uh, "Just dropped off
the cheating whor...
Lyndsey."
"Want to grab a drink?"
Okay, you go play
the sympathetic friend,
calm him down.
I'll figure sothing out.
Sounds good, uh...
"No problem, bro."
Uh...
Cocktail glass emoji.
Stall him as long as you can.
Right.
I'm sorry I kicked you
in the balls--
is there anything I can do?
You could kiss it
and make it better.
Good-bye, Alan.
Oh, come on!
It's not like I
could do it myself.
God knows I've tried.
(tires screeching)
Get in the car!
Rose?
What are you doing?
Someone's following you.
Yeah, you!
There's no time for this,
you're in danger.
Yeah, from you!
Just get in.
Why would I get in your car?
I mean, the last time
I tried to trust you...
What? What are you looking at?
You got a little spot
on your shirt.
Oh.
(screams)
Drive! Drive! Drive!
Drive! Drive!
I found out more
about this guy.
His name is
Walden Schmidt.
More like lying sack of Schmidt.
(chuckles)
Am I right?
Turns out he's some kind
of stupid Internet billionaire.
Don't you hate
when guys don't work
for a living like you and me?
Amen, Jeff Strongman.
Hey, come on, you know,
this isn't the worst thing
in the world.
You're gonna bounce back.
I guess, I mean,
I should've seen it coming.
I mean, she cheated
on her last boyfriend with me.
Her-her last boyfriend?
Yeah, I guess the guy
was a real loser.
A pathetic freeloader.
Well, that's just conjecture.
I mean, you know, maybe
he's a-a really great guy
and she's just
a crazy lying bitch.
I'm not gonna take it lying down
like the pansy
she was dating before me.
Is "pansy" your word or hers?
Hers.
I'm going to the head.
You get the check
and we'll go pay
this bastard a visit.
Take your time.
No rush.
Oh, come on, Lyndsey,
pick up, pick up, pick up!
(groans)
Of course, voice mail.
Lyndsey, things have gone
from bad to worse.
Larry is gonna confront Walden,
and I don't know what to do.
Call me back.
Oh, and PS-- you and I have
a little issue
to discuss ourselves.
Oh, and PPS--
the "P" stands for "pansy."
Mm-hmm.
Whew.
Looks like we lost him.
What the hell is going on?
Well, I'm pretty sure
Larry hired a hit man.
How do you know about Larry?
Because he's stalking you.
How do you know that?
Because I'm stalking you.
Okay, okay, you know,
this is ridiculous.
I'm calling the police.
And tell them what?
We have no proof
of anything.
And besides, how helpful
were the police
when you called them on me?
Uh, I got them to issue
a restraining order.
Hi.
Okay, I...
Uh-oh, he's back.
I don't know how he
keeps finding us.
I'll tell you how.
The GPS on my cell phone.
Give me that.
I was gonna turn it off,
but okay.
Hang on.
What? Why?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(squealing)
Whoa!
(sighs)
That ought to do it.
Okay, you know...
this is nonsense!
(stammers)
Take me home.
Okay, homeward bound.
And gagged.
And tortured for days.
Okay, well, fine,
then take me to a hotel.
Beverly Hills Hotel okay?
It's perfect.
And bang, you're dead.
You need to get
off the grid.
Someplace they
don't expect you.
A place they can't track
your credit cards.
Nobody is acking
my credit cards.
Oh, that wasn't you last night
getting a coffee colonic?
I will not apologize
for a healthy colon.
Okay, here we go.
This place looks perfect.
This place is a dump.
Exactly, and it's the last place
anyone would look for you.
Yeah, but it's the first place
that hepatitis
would look for me.
Okay, this is only temporary.
You lay low,
and I will straighten this out.
Why in God's name
would I trust you?
Look, Walden, I know
that I've caused you
some tiny problems
in the past, but...
Wha...? Tiny?
You pretended to be pregnant
to scare my girlfriend away.
You sicced rabid ferrets on me!
You tied me to my bed
and tried to violate me
with a leaf blower!
It's so sweet you
remember everything.
But I can make up
for all of that now.
Look, when your sink is clogged,
you call a plumber.
When your car breaks down,
you call a mechanic.
When you have a dangerous
psychopath after you,
you call me.
All right, fine.
I am gonna kill Alan.
Oh, if you survive tonight,
you should hire Larry's guy.
He's good.
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go.
This is, uh, this is
the best room you got?
It's the presidential suite.
The president of what?
Crap-o-slovakia?
I could offer you
the honeymoon suite.
You know, if you don't mind
the smell of love.
No, no... this is, uh...
this is fine.
Uh...
Do you, uh, do you
have room service?
I might have something
you might want to eat.
I don't think you do.
Listen, uh, if-if anyone
comes here asking about me,
I-I'm not here.
Don't worry.
No one will ever find you.
Hey, uh, if you get
lonely later on,
I'm in the apartment
behind the building.
Yeah, okay.
It's nothing fancy,
but I've got some good weed
and... a spa tub.
I'll, uh, keep that in mind.
There's a live feed
on channel 14
if you want to check it out.
(door closes)
Great, now I got
to hide from him, too.
This Walden guy is gonna regret
the day he stole my girlfriend.
Oh, it's-it's not stealing.
It-It's more like borrowing.
Like-like renting a car.
Yeah, but when you rent a car
you know there's been
other guys inside it,
turning the knobs,
playing with the seat,
shoving stuff in the trunk.
Okay, okay, maybe that's
a bad analogy.
But that doesn't change
the fact that going over there
to confront him is not
gonna help anything.
You got a better idea?
Uh, I-I do.
How about you forget
about Lyndsey
and we go out to a bar
and pick up some women.
You know, Larry and Jeff
out on the prowl.
(growls)
Jeff, I appreciate
what you're trying to do.
But I'm afraid
if I don't do this,
I won't be able
to live with myself.
And I'm afraid if you do this,
I'll have to live by myself.
(indistinct chatter on TV)
Oh, no! Channel 14!
Oh, God!
(knocking)
Who is it?
(deep voice): It's Larry, I'm here
to kill you, Walden.
Mr. Walden, he die.
I clean room.
ROSE:
No, silly rabbit, it's just me.
Wha...? Rose?
Is that...?
Are you alone?
Yeah, but a nice man did just
invite me into his spa tub.
Here, I brought some food.
Yeah, I can't eat.
Why not?
Well, because if I do,
eventually
I'll have to go in there.
And I'm not going in there.
Uh, so, did you find
anything out?
Still no sign of Larry.
He could be anywhere.
God, Alan was supposed
to take care of this.
Well, yeah, he also told you
he was only gonna live
at your house a few days, and
here we are at day 800 and...
43.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I t usgoome candy bars.
Mounds for you,
'cause it's your favorite.
Aw.
Almond Joy for me
'cause, you know... nuts.
Hey, why are you being
so nice to me?
You know,
I'll admit that you hurt me.
And I did some things
that I'm not proud of.
But just because
you took a restraining order
out against me...
doesn't mean that I can
restrain my feelings for you.
That is the sweetest,
most terrifying thing
I've ever heard.
Are you really
scared of me?
You're not even the scariest
person I've met in this room.
And the truth is,
I'm-I'm not blameless.
I mean, I chose
another girl over you,
and look who's here
with me now?
I never really left you.
Literally.
File this under things
I'm gonna regret.
Damn it, should've
brought my leaf blower.
Oh, uh,
the doorbell doesn't work.
What?
I mean, uh,
that-that does not work
if you want to send a message
that there's a man here.
♪ Ding-dong.
"I'm gonna kick your tushie."
You're right.
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay, now, listen,
now-now, this could get crazy.
I mean, there's gonna be
a lot of name calling--
uh, uh, jerk, uh, idiot,
uh, Alan.
Uh...
Larry?
Lyndsey?
I know exactly what's going on
between you and Walden Schmidt.
Now, where is he?
Wow! This house
is amazing.
Larry, this isn't
what you think.
It's exactly what I think.
I have pictures.
We're standing in his house!
Okay, it-it's time for me
to tell you the truth.
Don't believe her!
She's a cheating, drunk whore!
Larry, listen to me.
I'm not here to sleep
with Walden Schmidt.
I'm here to sleep
with someone else.
What?!
Remember you told me
your fantasy was
to see me with another woman?
Yeah?
I've arranged for your dream
to come true.
You did?!
Yes, that's why I rented
this beautiful beach house
from Walden Schmidt
as a birthday surprise.
I also got us something else.
So, which one is watching us?
If it's him, I'm gonna
have to charge extra.
Wait a minute.
Is this for real?
Happy birthday, baby.
Wow. Wow.
(laughs)
A threesome.
That is quite
a gift.
Well, it was last minute,
and I had to think of something.
A nice cardigan wouldn't
have done the trick?
God, I feel so stupid.
I even hired someone
to follow you.
Well, why don't you
call them off,
and we'll all go sit down
and talk about the things
you want to see?
Bye, Jeff.
Yeah, bye, Jeff.
I'll send you a
copy of the video.
Wait. Thi-Thi...
Wait. This is
really... happening?
I mean, you-you-you
and-and-and her?
And-and... and him?
And-and-and here?
While... while I...?
Son of a bitch!
(mutters)
This is crazy.
You know, I'll...
I'll bet
if Lyndsey had been sleeping
with somebody else,
he'd be really, really mad.
I know.
Isn't this great, Jeff?
She's not a cheating whore.
She's just a whore.
Hi. It's Larry Martin.
Oh, hey.
Listen, I'm not going to be
needing your services anymore,
but I appreciate all your help.
No problem.
It was my pleasure.
Good-bye.
That was Alan.
What did he say?
Well, he, uh, thanked me
for protecting you.
But there's still no sign
of Larry.
And as long as he's out there,
you're not safe.
I'm gonna go get us
some supplies.
No, don't go!
We're having a good time.
You're just a sticky
little honey bun, aren't you?
Now, don't try
to get in touch with anyone,
or Larry will kill you.
Kisses.
(sighs)
I got to go to the bathroom.
Screw it.
I'll just pee the bed.
(thunder rumbling)
(heavy footsteps)
Rose?
(loud jangling of keys)
All right, come on, Rose.
This... this...
It's not funny.
(thunder crackling)
Larry?!
Listen, we can... we can...
we can work this out!
It's-it's just
a little misunderstanding.
(door rattling)
Oh, God! I...
(door rattling loudly)
Well, that was rude.
Looks like I took a shower
for nothing.
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Come out, come out,
wherever you are! ♪
I hate you, Jeff Strongman.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man